filecm.net 2014-02-08

# AdShift | Exclusive Affiliate Network, Incentivized Traffic & Content Locking

**AdShift Media Ltd Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to adshiftmedia.com's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by AdShift Media Ltd. Ltd on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the Website), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to AdShift Media Ltd's other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties. 

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website and our practices only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. 

**Use Of Cookies**

AdShift Media Ltd uses cookies to identify the individual with his or her corresponding tracking data that resides in AdShift Media Ltd's database. Individuals who use the Website need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Website. For EU residents, by using the Website you accept the use of cookies by us under the EU 2012 modification to the EU Privacy and Electronic Communications Directive. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

**Tracking Data**

To ensure we can provide a fraud-free service, AdShift Media Ltd's lead tracking system gathers IP addresses and other user variables along with setting tracking cookies. We use this information to prevent users from abusing advertiser terms and conditions, for example by doing multiple completions per person (regardless of IP address). 

**Use Of Web Beacon Technology**

A web beacon is a small pixel image that is placed on a website or in an email which is used to monitor behaviour of a user visiting a website or email and store their information. This allows AdShift Media Ltd to track certain websites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioural habits for marketing purposes. 

**Outside Information**

AdShift Media Ltd may receive information about individuals from Third Parties or from other sources of information outside of AdShift Media Ltd including information located in public databases (Outside Information). 

**Individual Information**

As used herein, Individual Information means Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information AdShift Media Ltd gathers or receives about individuals such as usage data, file transfer and viewing data. 

**In Regards to Deleting & Updating Your Information**

If you would like to delete or update the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you (name, address, etc.), simply send your request to support@adshiftmedia.com. We will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings if requested. 

**Regarding The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)**

AdShift Media Ltd will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If AdShift Media Ltd obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database and any hard copies will be destroyed. Because it does not collect such information, AdShift Media Ltd has no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. AdShift Media Ltd has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). 

**Legal Process**

AdShift Media Ltd may disclose Individual Information to respond to court orders and other legal processes to any UN member court. 

**Regarding Fraudulent Activity & Scamming**

It is AdShift Media Ltd's right to close or dismiss any clients or accounts without pay if AdShift Media Ltd has a suspicion of fraudulent activity or a suspicion of scam. We employ many measures to prevent fraud, although some fraud is more difficult to detect. As a publisher or advertiser it is your duty to limit the fraudulent activity that appears on your account. AdShift Media Ltd holds the right to display relevant account details with third parties to verify or investigate fraudulent activity. 

**Advertiser Cookies and Web Beacons**

AdShift Media Ltd does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and AdShift Media Ltd has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. 

**Links**

The Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of Third Parties. AdShift Media Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. AdShift Media Ltd does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third Party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. 

**Notation For International Clients**

Anyone using the Website outside of the United Kingdom acknowledges that personal information will be collected and stored by AdShift Media Ltd in the United Kingdom. By using the Website, you consent to the transfer of information to and/or storage of information outside of your country and in the United Kingdom. 

**Information collected from Third Parties**

AdShift Media Ltd collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and AdShift Media Ltd subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the Seller). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, postal code, telephone numbers (including mobile phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, Third Party List Information). When acquiring Third Party List Information, AdShift Media Ltd seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to AdShift Media Ltd and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list. 

**Contact**

If you have any questions or comments related to this privacy policy please contact us.   
(kyle@adshiftmedia.com)
